https://www.harristate.co.nz/privacy

Our areas of expertise
Expertise
Business LawElder LawEmployment LawFamily LawFranchisingImmigrationInsolvency / BankruptcyLitigation and Dispute ResolutionMaori Legal IssuesNotary PublicPersonal LawPropertyRelationship Property
About us
About Us
Our Story
Our People
DirectorsLegal TeamManagement
Client stories
Client Stories
Tony Han OptometristGJ Gardner HomesMcLeod CranesMcDonalds TaurangaWestbay WaratahsCarrus Corporation LtdKelowna Group
Articles
Latest News
Residential Care Subsidy and changes to Trust LawNew Trusts Act UpdateChanges to Tenancy LegislationImmigration UpdateCovid-19 Alert Level 2COVID-19 Companies Act and insolvencyCOVID-19 Issues for MaoriCommercial lease obligations and COVID-19COVID-19 Voidable TransactionsCOVID-19 and Family LawCOVID-19 Employment law updateHarris Tate and level 4 alertCounting down to a major overhaul of Trust LawParent category visa to reopen in February 2020Immigration policy changesWant to Buy a Commercial Building?10 facts regarding Enduring Powers of AttorneyWhat happens if you die without a Will?Transferable development rightsProperty law changesKeeping criminals outAn announcement from Harris TateGetting to know you... getting to know all about youThe Swing of the PendulumRighting the wrongEstate planning for property investorsAre Trusts Still Relevant for Property Investors?Minor dwelling or subdivisionTenant's Intentional DamageLure of home proves irresistible to solicitor and young familyThe power of putting your assets in safe handsSeize the chance to jump on the trampoline revolutionPlenty of action in the Western Bay: Tauranga taking on a new lookLooking the part in the eye of the lawTighter migrant laws set to hinder the regionsA hive of legal activityLegally Sweet. The law firm and the humble honeybeeHarris Tate promotes Michelle Carabine to AssociateMethamphetamine Contamination. To test or not to test?Time to future-proof your familySqueeze goes on property investors under tough new restrictionsSpick and span advice from award-winning franchiseTauranga takes centre stage at New Zealand Franchise ConferenceTwo into one will go. An overview of land subdivisionTighter rules on property investors unveiledTenancy Act shake-up set to keep tenants warmer and saferWhat you need to know: new insulation and smoke alarm regulations for rental propertiesHarris Tate takes day off for a good causeResidential Land Witholding Tax changes from July 1NZ Trusts inadvertently caught by US tax regimeA classic recipe for franchise successDecision Making in Senior YearsLocal law firm answers mayday call from Tauranga CoastguardIs a family trust still worthwhile in 2016?Thailand trip to shed light on animal atrocitiesBack to school before business migrationTauranga's newest solicitor shows it's never too late to make a legal dream a realityTauranga solicitor takes out highly coveted Environmental Law prizeDon't get left out in the cold with new tenancies lawsEnsuring there are no smoke mirrorsThe hidden costs of buying investment propertyShining a light on taxable property profitsAvoid the Christmas party legal hangoverDoes a life interest have a value if you need residential care?Who should make decisions for me when I can't?Knowing the right language when it comes to lawWhen should a trustee retire?
Community
Mountain Bike TaurangaChild Cancer FoundationTauranga City United FootballBOP Film Inc.Tauranga Property Investors AssociationBay of Plenty Chinese Business & Commerce AssociationAge Concern TaurangaAuckland Youth OrchestraTauranga Volunteer Coastguard AssociationColour Dash - Ronald McDonald House, Project K, KidsCanSummerhill A1 Youth Academy
Contact
Contact
Smart Law.
Intelligent Advice
T 07 578 0059
F 07 578 2692
HARRIS TATE LAWYERS
29 Brown Street
Tauranga 3110, New Zealand
Call us today 07 578 0059
Privacy
PERSONAL INFORMATION
We collect personally identifiable information. Providing this information will always be optional for you. However, some services may not be available to you if you chose not to provide it.
From time to time, we may run contests or other promotions. If you participate, we may request your name, mailing address, email address and other information in order to administer the promotion. When you submit a request, review or comment to our customer service department, we may ask you for your email address.
We also collect aggregated data. This information is generated by our systems as they track traffic through our sites. This information does not identify you personally and is not linked to the personally identifiable information that you may have provided.
USES AND DISCLOSURE – MORE INFORMATION
Who do we share this information with?
We will not share the information that we collect with any third parties. The information may be hosted with a service provider. Our agreements with them protect the information that we collect from any use by them that we have not authorised.
The aggregated data (not the personally identifiable information) may be shared with third parties such as advertisers or business partners.
How do we use the information?
When you register, complete a form or participate in any contest or promotion on our website, we will use the information you provided to us to send you email or regular mail from us regarding products, services or other contests and promotions that we think may be of interest to you.
We may use the data to verify your identity if you need help with a forgotten password, or you are having logon difficulties with any of our site services.
From time to time we may aggregate your information analyse trends, preferences, and demographics. We may use the information for other purposes with your prior permission.
How do we use "cookies"?
"Cookies" are small pieces of information stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Cookies do not contain personally identifying information. It does provide details of your IP address, the computer platform that you use (eg Mac or Windows), the browser that you use (eg Microsoft Explorer or Netscape) and what domain you are accessing our sites from. With this information we can do the following:
Track traffic patterns to our site.
Ensure that the most relevant content is being shown.
Allow you to enter certain site member services without having to log in each time you visit.
Most web browsers are set up to accept cookies; you can usually change your browser settings to refuse cookies. You will still be able to visit our sites with cookies disabled.
Google Advertising
We may use cookies to collect data for Google remarketing purposes for online advertising. We make every effort to abide by all Google Advertising policies. Third-party vendors, including Google, may show our ads across other sites on the Internet.
Cookies stored by your browser may be used by third-party vendors, including Google, to show you ads based on your previous website activity, including visits to our website
Can we change this policy?
In order to reflect the fact that our business is growing constantly, we reserve the right to change this policy at any time. Please refer to Last Updated
CONTACT US
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with Harris Tate, you can contact us.
Keep up to date
Sign up to receive updates and news from Harris Tate
Your subscription could not be saved. Please try again.
Your subscription has been successful.
HARRIS TATE LAWYERS29 Brown StreetTauranga 3110, New Zealand
Copyright © 2018 - 2020 Harris Tate. All rights reserved. Terms of Engagement | Privacy | Sitemap | Website by MOCA
